Guide to the Graduate School Records, 1924-2014 UA.24.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1924-1994 and undated
  - Woodrow Wilson, Dissertation Fellowship Program, 1963-1964 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship, 1963-1964 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson, Summer, 1964 (Box 66)
  - Woosley, John B., 1945 (Box 66)
  - Zoology Department, 1946-1949 (Box 66)
  - Zoology Department (Box 66)
  - Zoology Department, 1955-1958 (Box 66)
  - Microbiology (Box 66)
  - Mechanical Engineering (Box 66)
  - Accession UA70-59. Dissertation Abstracts, 1956-1962 (Box 67)
    This subseries consists of abstracts of dissertations written at Duke between 1956 and 1962. Starting in 1963, abstracts were bound at the front of dissertations rather than filed separately.
    - Dissertation Abstracts A-J (Box 67)
    - Dissertation Abstracts K-Z (Box 68)
  - Graduate School Newsletter, The (v.1 no.1), 1988 Fall (Box 69)
  - Graduate School Report (v.1 no.1-v.3 no.4) c.1, 1969 Sept.-1972 May (Box 69)
  - Graduate School Report, Newsletter (v.1 no.1-v.3 no.4) c.2, 1969-1972 (Box 69)
  - Alumni Newsletter (Box 69)
  - Clippings (Box 69)
  - Fellowships, Scholarships, and Assistantships (Box 69)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (3 Folders) (Box 69)
  - Religion Department, 1972-1977 (Box 69)
  - Miscellaneous Memos to Graduate Faculty, 1944-1971 June (Box 70)
  - Miscellaneous Memos to Graduate Faculty, 1971 Aug.-1980 Sept. (Box 70)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (scattered issues), 1941 Apr.-1962 June (Box 70)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (scattered issues), 1962 Oct.-1971 May (Box 70)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (incomplete), 1971 Sept.-1975 May (Box 70)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (incomplete/complete from Sept. 1978), 1975 Sept.-1980 Jan. (Box 71)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (incomplete/complete from Sept. 1978), 1980-1981 (Box 71)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (incomplete/complete from Sept. 1978), 1981-1984 (Box 71)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (incomplete/complete from Sept. 1978), 1984-1987 (Box 71)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (incomplete/complete from Sept. 1978), 1987-1988 (Box 71)
  - Graduate Faculty and Executive Committee Minutes and Related Memos (incomplete/complete from Sept. 1978), 1994 Apr. 19 (Box 71)
- Accession UA74-82, 1960-1973
  Files from the office of the Dean of the Graduate School.
  - Administrative Committee, 1961-1963 (Box 72)
  - Administrative Council Meetings, 1967 Sept.-1969 Feb. (Box 72)
  - African and Afro-American Studies Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 72)
  - Biological Science Council, 1963-1964 (Box 72)
  - Biological Science Council, 1964-1966 (Box 72)
  - Biological Science Council, 1970 -1971 (Box 72)
  - International Studies, Committee on, Minutes of Meetings, 1965-1973 (Box 72)
  - International Studies, Committee on, Duke University, 1965 (Box 72)
  - International Studies, Committee on, Duke University, 1966 (Box 72)
  - International Studies, Committee on, Duke University, 1967 (Box 72)
  - International Studies, Committee on, Duke University, 1968 Jan.-1968 Mar. (Box 72)
  - Cooperative Program, Duke and UNC, Graduate School Summer Terms, 1961-1967 (Box 72)
  - Cooperative Program in Humanities, Duke and UNC, 1963-1964 (Box 72)
  - Cooperative Program in Humanities, Duke and UNC, 1964-1965 (Box 72)
  - Cooperative Program in Humanities, Duke and UNC, 1967-1968 (Box 72)
  - Cooperative Program in International Studies, Duke and UNC, 1966-1969 (Box 72)
  - Cooperative Program in Library, Duke and UNC, 1964 (Box 72)
  - Cooperative Program in Undergraduate, Duke and UNC, 1961-1964 (Box 72)
  - Memorandum, J. C. McKinney to Mareus Hobbs, on the responsibilities of the graduate Dean, 1969 Feb. 27 (Box 73)
  - Cooperative Program in Winchester Excavations, Duke and UNC, 1964-1965 (Box 73)
  - Financial Support of Graduate Students (Box 73)
  - Graduate School Faculty Meeting (Box 73)
  - Honors - Masters Program, 1961-1965 (Box 73)
  - Humanities Council, Duke University, 1959-1969 (Box 73)
  - Institutional Studies, Long-Range Planning, 1961-1962 (Box 73)
  - Medical Center, Duke University, Long-Range Planning, vol. 1, 1961 (Box 73)
  - Medical Center, Duke University, Long-Range Planning, vol. 2, 1961 (Box 73)
  - Provost Group, 1967-1968, 1971-1972 (Box 73)
  - Aging and Human Development, Center for, Search Committee for Director, 1972 (Box 73)
- Accession UA77-133, 1960-1976
  Files from the office of the Dean of the Graduate School; much of it is printed material distributed by the Dean to graduate faculty and to the Directors of Graduate Studies of the various departments.
  - Summer Visiting Scholars Grants-in-Aid, 1965-1972 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Student Association (GSA), 1968-1969, 1972-1973 (Box 74)
  - Educational Administration Advisory Group (Provost Group), 1971 Fall (Box 74)
  - Trustees, Board of, Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 74)
  - Trustees, Board of, Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 74)
  - Trustees, Board of, Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 74)
  - Trustees, Board of, Meetings, 1977 Jan.-1977 June (Box 74)
  - Bulgarian Academy Visitors, 1973 Nov. (Box 74)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH) Grants, Budgeting of Funds, 1972 (Box 74)
  - Sponsored Programs Study by Dr. Linda Wilson, Washington University, Saint Louis, 1971 (Box 74)
  - Sponsored Research at Princeton, 1970-1971 (Box 74)
  - Sponsored Programs at Duke University, 1970 (Box 74)
  - Discontinuance of Surplus Property to Government Grantees, Impact on Duke of (Bill S. 948), 1973 (Box 74)
  - Research Triangle Foundation Grant Program, 1968-1970 (Box 74)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, Memos to, 1973-1974 (Box 74)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, Memos to, 1972-1973 (Box 74)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, Memos to, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1973-1974 (Box 74)
  - Science and Technology, North Carolina Board of, 1963, 1974, 1975 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1969-1970 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1970-1971 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, 1974-1975 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1958 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1962-1968 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Meetings, 1973-1974 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Memos to, 1974-1975 (Box 74)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1972-1974 (Box 74)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1970-1972 (Box 74)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1957-1970 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1973-1974 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1972-1973 (Box 74)
  - Trustees, Board of, Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 74)
  - Educational Administration Advisory Group (Provost Group), 1969-1971 (Box 74)
  - Council of Graduate Schools in the U.S. (CGS), 1972 (Box 74)
  - Council of Southern Universities, 1968-1974 (Box 74)
  - Visiting Scholars, The Graduate School, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - Advisory Committee, The Cooperative Program in Teacher Education, Master of Art in Teaching (MAT) (Box 74)
  - Aging and Human Development and Center for Aging and Human Development, University Council on, 20th Anniversary Committee (Box 74)
  - Public Education and the Training of Teachers, University Committee on, 1970-1971 (Box 74)
  - Summer Session Advisory Committee (Box 74)
  - Ecology, National Institute of (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1971-1976 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1970-1971 (Box 74)
  - Richardson, Secretary Elliot, Visit to Duke University, 1971 Mar. (Box 74)
  - Higher Education Bill, 1971-1972 (Box 74)
  - Conference, "The Future of Graduate Education" (Box 75)
  - Graduate Student Association Newsletter (Box 75)
  - Graduate School Enrollment (Box 75)
  - Graduate School Procedures, Recommended Changes in (Box 75)
  - Electrical Engineering, Plan for Program of Graduate Work in the Department of (Box 75)
  - Hospital Administration, Proposal for Graduate Program in (Box 75)
  - Visiting Scholars, The Graduate School, 1973-1974 (Box 75)
  - Visiting Scholars, The Graduate School, 1972-1973 (Box 75)
  - Faculty Projections, Committee on, 1965-1966 (Box 75)
  - Visiting Scholars, The Graduate School, 1975-1976 (Box 75)
  - Visiting Scholars, The Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 75)
  - Registration, 1972-1973 (Box 75)
  - Registration, 1971-1972 (Box 75)
  - Registration, 1970-1971 (Box 75)
  - Registration, 1969-1970 (Box 75)
  - Registration, 1974-1975 (Box 75)
  - Registration, 1973-1974 (Box 75)
  - Social Science Council, 1964-1968 (Box 75)
  - Biological Science Council, 1964-1968 (Box 75)
  - Intermediate Graduate Degree, Consideration of, 1966 (Box 75)
  - Language Requirements Committee, 1968 (Box 75)
  - NDFL - NDEA, 1961-1962 (Box 75)
  - Committee to Approve and Review New Programs in Humanities, 1962 (Box 75)
  - Earth Sciences, Committee on (Duke-UNC-NCSU), 1961-1963 (Box 75)
  - Summer Session Advisory Committee, 1962-1970 (Box 75)
  - Oceanography, Proposed Doctoral Program in, 1966-1967 (Box 75)
  - Duke - UNC National Security Affairs Program Proposal, 1960 (Box 75)
  - Cytology Training, Proposed Program, 1962 (Box 75)
  - Foreign Students List, 1964 (Box 75)
  - Education, American Council on, 1964-1969 (Box 75)
  - Association of Graduate Schools (AGS), 1960-1971 (Box 75)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Manual for (Box 75)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Symposium, 1974-1975 (Box 75)
  - National Board on Graduate Education (Box 75)
- Accession UA80-200, 1959-1978 and undated
  Most of the materials in this series concerns or is connected with the administration of John C. McKinney, Dean of the Graduate School from 1970.
  - Affirmative Action Information and Statistics, Duke University, 1972 (Box 76)
  - Affirmative Action, Duke University, 1969-1972 (Box 76)
  - Sponsored Research, Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 76)
  - Sponsored Research, Miscellaneous, 1965-1970 (Box 76)
  - Restricted Funds, Analysis of, Duke University, 1967-1971 (Box 76)
  - Restricted Funds, Overdrafts on Current, 1971 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Research Sub-Grants, 1972-1973 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Research Sub-Grants, 1971-1972 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), 1970-1971 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Miscellaneous, 1968-1970 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Summer Trainees, 1972 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Summer Trainees, 1971 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Summer Trainees, 1970 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Summer Trainees, 1969 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Summer Trainees, 1968 (Box 76)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Summer Trainees, 1967 (Box 76)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH), Grants Policy Statement, 1967-1970 (Box 76)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Expenditure Ceiling, 1971-1972 (Box 77)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Expenditure Ceiling, 1970-1971 (Box 77)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Expenditure Ceiling, 1969-1970 (Box 77)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Research Applied to National Needs (RANN) Program, 1971-1973 (Box 77)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Research Initiation and Support (RIAS), 1976 (Box 77)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Supplementary Proposal - University Science Development Program, 1972 Feb. (Box 77)
  - National Science Foundation (NSF), Science Development Program, 1969-1970 (Box 77)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), 1973-1974 (Box 77)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), Subgrant Progress Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 77)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG) (4 Folders), 1974-1975 (Box 77)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant (BSSG), 1975-1976 (Box 77)
  - Supply and Demand for Ph.D.s, 1971 (Box 77)
  - Supply and Demand for Ph.D.s, 1972 (Box 78)
  - Special Task Force: Assessment of Impact on Duke of Possible Elimination of National Institute of Health (NIH) Training Grants (Box 78)
  - National Institute of Health (NIH) / National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH) Training Program Reports (Box 78)
  - Bibliography Regarding Manpower and Graduate Education, 1971 (Box 78)
  - Provost Group, 1977-1978 (Box 78)
  - Provost Group, 1976-1977 (Box 78)
  - Provost Group, 1974-1976 (Box 78)
  - Provost Group, 1972-1974 (Box 78)
  - President, Report to the, 1970-1972 (Box 78)
  - Newman Report, The, 1971 (Box 78)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1976-1977 (Box 78)
  - Sanford, Terry; Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 78)
  - National Program of Institutional Grants (Box 78)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges, 1971 (Box 78)
  - Epoch Campaign, The, 1973 (Box 78)
  - Electric Power Research Institute (EPRI), 1973-1975 (Box 78)
  - Educational Testing Service (ETS), Foreign Language Testing Program, 1963-1974 (Box 78)
  - Educational Testing Service (ETS), 1972-1974 (Box 78)
  - Institute of Education, 1977 (Box 78)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, 1976-1977 (Box 78)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, Memos to, 1976-1977 (Box 78)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, 1975-1976 (Box 78)
  - Directors of Graduate Studies, Memos to, 1975-1976 (Box 78)
  - Southern Regional Growth Board, 1971 (Box 78)
  - Trustee Meetings, 1977-1979 (Box 78)
  - Southern Studies, Center for (Box 78)
  - Trustees, Report to; Miscellaneous Information about the Graduate School Including some Relevant Historical Material, 1976 (Box 78)
  - Financial Aid, 1970 (Box 78)
  - Gross, Paul M., The Potential of Higher Education and a Pattern for Its Development During the Next Fifteen Years, 1959 (Box 78)
  - Carter, Allan M., The Decades Ahead: Trends and Problems, Graduate Education Today, 1963 (Box 78)
  - Graduate School, The, 1959 (Box 78)
  - Berkner, L. V., Whither Graduate Education?, 1963 (Box 78)
  - The Status and Needs of the Private University for Meeting the Task Ahead, with Special Reference to Graduate Education (Box 78)
  - Miscellaneous Information Concerning Graduate Education and Science Indicators, 1973 Sept. 10 (Box 78)
  - Association of American Universities (AAU) Resolution, Federal Support of Graduate Education, 1972 May 9 (Box 78)
- Accession UA83-19, 1963-1982 and undated
  - American Council on Education, 1975-1978 (Box 79)
  - Budget, Graduate Awards, 1977-1978 (Box 79)
  - Budget, Graduate Awards, 1976-1977 (Box 79)
  - Budgets, Graduate School Office, 1977-1978 (Box 79)
  - Budgets, Graduate School Office, 1976-1977 (Box 79)
  - Budget, Graduate Awards, 1976-1977 (Box 79)
  - Budget, Graduate Awards, 1974-1975 (Box 79)
  - Budget, Graduate Awards, 1973-1974 (Box 79)
  - Budgets, Graduate School Office, 1975-1976 (Box 79)
  - Budgets, Graduate School Office, 1974-1975 (Box 79)
  - Budgets, Graduate School Office, 1973-1974 (Box 79)
  - Commencement, 1973-1976 (Box 79)
  - Commencement, Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 79)
  - Graduate Schools, Council of (CGS) in the U.S., 1977-1979 (Box 79)
  - Graduate Schools, Council of (CGS) in the U.S., 1975-1977 (Box 79)
  - Graduate Schools, Council of (CGS), Graduate Cost Study, 1974 (Box 79)
  - Employee and Post-Doc Opportunities to National Research Council, Department Reports on (National Academy of Sciences) (Box 79)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, 1978-1979 (Box 79)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Memos to, 1978-1979 (Box 79)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, 1977-1978 (Box 79)
  - Graduate Studies, Directors of, Memos to, 1977-1978 (Box 79)
  - Federal Relations Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 79)
  - Federal Relations Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 79)
  - Federal Relations Organizations of Universities, 1973 (Box 79)
  - Tuition and Fees, 1962-1970 (Box 79)
  - Applications, 1954-1958 (Box 80)
  - Departmental Review, 1976 (Box 80)
  - McKinney, Dr. John C. (Box 80)
  - Departmental Review, 1975 June (Box 80)
  - Departmental Review, 1974 (Box 80)
  - Departmental Review, 1971-1973 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, Graduate School, 1971-1972 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, Graduate School, 1970-1971 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, Graduate School, 1969-1970 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, Graduate School, 1967-1968 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, Graduate School, 1962-1963 (Box 80)
  - Miscellaneous; Graduate Schools in General, Financial Crisis, Organization, etc. (Box 80)
  - Academic Deans Conference, 1975-1978 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, Graduate School, 1975-1976 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 80)
  - Advisory Committee, Council of Graduate Schools/Institute of International Education (CGS/IIE), 1976 (Box 80)
  - Advisory Committee, Council of Graduate Schools/Institute of International Education (CGS/IIE), 1975 (Box 80)
  - Advisory Committee, Council of Graduate Schools/Institute of International Education (CGS/IIE), 1974 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1978-1979 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1977-1978 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1976-1977 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1974-1975 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1973-1974 (Box 80)
  - Admissions, 1972-1973 (Box 80)
  - Alumni, 1975-1979 (Box 80)
  - Application Trends and Enrollment, Vanderbilt Study, 1975-1980 (Box 80)
  - Bulletins Committee, University, 1979-1980 (Box 80)
  - Commencement, 1977-1980 (Box 80)
  - Executive Committee, Graduate Faculty, 1977-1978 (Box 80)
  - Executive Committee, Graduate Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 80)
  - Executive Committee, Graduate Faculty, 1975-1976 (Box 80)
  - Affirmative Action, 1974-1975 (Box 80)
  - Affirmative Action, 1973-1974 (Box 80)
  - Affirmative Action, 1972-1973 (Box 80)
  - Resource and Environmental Policy Research, Center for (Box 81)
  - Fellowship and Research Support, Resources for, 1980-1981 (Box 81)
  - Fellowship and Research Support, Resources for, 1978-1980 (Box 81)
  - Fellowship and Research Support, Resources for, 1976-1978 (Box 81)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1970-1979 (Box 81)
  - Graduate Awards, Supplementation of (Box 81)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1979-1980 (Box 81)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1978-1979 (Box 81)
  - Visiting Scholars, 1977-1978 (Box 81)
  - College Work-Study, 1978-1979 (Box 81)
  - College Work-Study, 1977-1978 (Box 81)
  - College Work-Study, 1976-1977 (Box 81)
  - College Work-Study, 1974-1976 (Box 81)
  - Organization of Tropical Studies (OTS), 1976-1977 (Box 81)
  - Organization of Tropical Studies (OTS), 1975-1976 (Box 81)
  - Organization of Tropical Studies (OTS), 1971-1974 (Box 81)
  - Pessar, Dr. Patricia, NICHD Grant (Box 81)
  - Promotion and Tenure, Advisory Committee on, 1969-1979 (Box 81)
  - Registration, 1980-1981 (Box 81)
  - Registration, 1977-1980 (Box 81)
  - Registration, 1975-1977 (Box 81)
  - Registration Expediter's Group (Box 81)
  - Humanists' Careers, James Henderson, 1977-1978 (Box 81)
  - Ad Hoc Committee on the Neurosciences, 1976-1978 (Box 81)
  - Rural Health Coalition, North Carolina (Box 81)
  - Organization of Tropical Studies (OTS), 1977-1979 (Box 81)
  - Foreign Language Requirement, 1963-1976 (Box 81)
  - Foreign Language Self-Study Program Proposal (Box 81)
  - Foreign Policy Institute Proposal (Box 81)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1974-1976 (Box 81)
  - Graduate Faculty, Memos to, 1976-1979 (Box 81)
  - Graduate Student Association, 1973 (Box 81)
  - University Review Committee on the Use of Human Subjects in Non-Medical Research, 1966-1978 (Box 81)
- Accession UA85-36, 1970-1984 and undated
  Information regarding grant programs.
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1975-1976 (Box 82)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1974-1975 (Box 82)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1973-1974 (Box 82)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1972-1973 (Box 82)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1971-1972 (Box 82)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 82)
  - Biomedical Sciences Support Grant, 1969-1970 (Box 82)
  - Science and Public Affairs, Round Table on: American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) Congressional Science and Engineering Fellows, 1973-1980 (Box 82)
  - Science and Public Affairs, Round Table on: American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS) Congressional Science and Engineering Fellows, 1980-1984 (Box 82)
  - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program (GPOP), Application, 1985-1986 (Box 82)
  - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program (GPOP), Application, 1984-1985 (Box 82)
  - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program (GPOP), 1983-1984 (Box 82)
  - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program (GPOP), Name Exchange Program, 1983 (Box 82)
  - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program (GPOP), 1982-1983 (Box 82)
  - Graduate and Professional Opportunities Program (GPOP), 1981-1982 (Box 82)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Training Grant, Psychology, Public Policy and Prevention #302-7356-, 1982-1983 (Box 82)
  - Graduate School Report (Box 82)
  - Grant, William T., Foundation, Postdoctoral Legislative Training Program for Behavioral Scientists #392-28090, 1977 Nov. 1-1984 June 30 (Box 82)
  - MacArthur, John D. and Catherine T., Foundation Grant, 1984 Summer Stipends for 2 Postdoctoral Trainees on the Round Table on Science and Public Affairs #382-5018, Summer, 1984 (Box 82)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Training Grant, Application for, 1983-1984 (Box 82)
  - Science and Public Affairs, Round Table on, #157-1115- -11100 (Box 82)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Training Grant #302-7341, 1981-1982 (Box 82)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, Reports of, 1979-1981 (Box 82)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, Reports of, 1978-1980 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, 1978-1980 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, Reports of, 1977-1979 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Training Grant, Training Behavioral Scientists in the Legislative Setting #5 T0 1 MH14383-, 1977-1979 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, 1977-1979 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, Reports of, 1976-1978 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, 1979-1981 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Training Grant, Training Behavioral Scientists in the Legislative Setting #5 T0 1 MH14383-, 1979-1981 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Training Grant, Training Behavioral Scientists in the Legislative Setting #5 T0 1 MH14383-, 1976-1977 (Box 83)
  - National Institute of Mental Health (NIMH), Postdoctoral Trainees, 1976-1978 (Box 83)
  - Science and Public Affairs, Round Table on, 1975-1976 (Box 83)
  - Science and Public Affairs, Round Table on, 1974-1975 (Box 83)
- Accession UA85-67, 1964-1970